<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://en.essepost.com//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://en.essepost.com//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2021-05-24T11:55:20+09:00</updated><id>https://en.essepost.com//feed.xml</id><title type="html">essepost</title><subtitle>IT, technology, up-to-date trends, and useful information</subtitle><author><name>essepost</name><email>deepseabolt@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">What is tapering? Impact on the stock market.</title><link href="https://en.essepost.com//2021/05/24/tapering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is tapering? Impact on the stock market." /><published>2021-05-24T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2021-05-24T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>https://en.essepost.com//2021/05/24/tapering</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://en.essepost.com//2021/05/24/tapering.html">&lt;p&gt;The market is keen on when Powell’s quantitative easing will end.&lt;br /&gt;
The beginning of quantitative easing will be tapering.&lt;br /&gt;
Tapering means that it is gradually decreasing.&lt;br /&gt;
It is the beginning of an exit strategy away from quantitative easing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/tapering/output (2).jpg&quot; alt=&quot;output&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;180&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to reduce the currency on the market.&lt;br /&gt;
Interest rate hikes, bond issuance, etc.&lt;br /&gt;
At the moment, we will not be able to drastically reduce the market currency sharply.&lt;br /&gt;
It is said that the economy is recovering, but the economy due to Corona is still unknown.&lt;br /&gt;
The long-term quantitative easing policy of the U.S. also puts pressure on currencies.&lt;br /&gt;
Tapering is about reducing the amount of money that increases as calls increase.&lt;br /&gt;
How?&lt;br /&gt;
In the meantime, large amounts of bond purchases are gradually reduced.&lt;br /&gt;
In other words, tapering is about reducing bond purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have experienced tapering in the past.&lt;br /&gt;
There was Chairman Ben Bernanke, nicknamed “Helicopter Ben.”&lt;br /&gt;
He argued that if the economy was in trouble, we should boost the economy even by spraying money with helicopters.&lt;br /&gt;
When the global financial market panicked in 2008 due to the Lehman Brothers crisis, the company pulled out quantitative easing cards.&lt;br /&gt;
His popularity was very high.&lt;br /&gt;
Ritually, he was appointed by the Republican government and served a second term in the Democratic government.&lt;br /&gt;
His successor, Powell, must have borne the burden of quantitative easing, and has so far adhered to the policy of quantitative easing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, inflation is a problem.&lt;br /&gt;
If there are more currencies on the market, the value of the currency falls and prices rise.&lt;br /&gt;
Rising prices reduce corporate investment and reduce employment.&lt;br /&gt;
So, ever since quantitative easing, there are always opinions here and there that are wary of inflation.&lt;br /&gt;
“At a time when the economy is recovering after the pandemic,” Federal Reserve Bank President Rafael Bostick told Bloomberg TV.&lt;br /&gt;
“I’m leaving every possibility open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was there no tapering in the past?&lt;br /&gt;
On May 23, 2013,&lt;br /&gt;
Chairman Ben Bernanke first mentioned tapering.&lt;br /&gt;
In June, a detailed roadmap was announced.&lt;br /&gt;
At that time, the S&amp;amp;P 500 also experienced a decline of 5 percent compared to its high point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From now on, it’s my idea.&lt;br /&gt;
Currently, the increase rate of raw material prices such as iron ore is too high.&lt;br /&gt;
Key figures in charge of the national economy must be afraid of high inflation.&lt;br /&gt;
If the current rate of increase in raw material prices continues, tapering will take place.
It will have a bad effect on the stock market.&lt;br /&gt;
However, the current economy is a new business.&lt;br /&gt;
There are various themes such as electric vehicles, metabuses, blockchain, and space industry.&lt;br /&gt;
These themes will give investors hope.&lt;br /&gt;
Always listen to market conditions and study.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>essepost</name><email>deepseabolt@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">The market is keen on when Powell’s quantitative easing will end. The beginning of quantitative easing will be tapering. Tapering means that it is gradually decreasing. It is the beginning of an exit strategy away from quantitative easing.</summary></entry></feed>